<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Karl&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Karl&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>karl.hepworth@gmail.com (Karl Hepworth)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>karl.hepworth@gmail.com (Karl Hepworth)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-reflection for 2019</title>
      <link>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/post/2018-12-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karl.hepworth@gmail.com (Karl Hepworth)</author>
      <guid>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/post/2018-12-25/</guid>
      <description>I started 2018 believing I could achieve reinventing myself, like so many did.
I was a fool because no matter the circumstance, a holiday is a great catalyst for this.
Reinventing myself included short-term goals and contributing progress to long-term goals. Each of these milestones were hindered by my employer in varying degrees.
The first part of the year was incredibly dull in a professional sense. Somewhere along the line I got fed up of waiting for things to happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The barrier of entry</title>
      <link>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/post/2018-11-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karl.hepworth@gmail.com (Karl Hepworth)</author>
      <guid>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/post/2018-11-14/</guid>
      <description>Not too long ago, one of DrupalACT&amp;rsquo;s developers made a blog post suggesting a developer is not just a developer anymore.
The author maintains the fact proudly that they&amp;rsquo;re probably being a bit grumpy, however there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of merit in this line of thought.
When starting out, it was all about the full-stack developer - the LAMP developer. The fact is, a full stack developer simply has a well-rounded set of skills for a particular type of technology which is usually centric to a given language or technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>karl.hepworth@gmail.com (Karl Hepworth)</author>
      <guid>https://fubarhouse.github.io/blog/page/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Karl Hepworth, and I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of an enthusiast of software, software tooling and generally fun stuff in the digital age. I love working on tooling, automation and things which support people to do fun work. I also love back-end development, but I don&amp;rsquo;t get many chances.
I do work for a government in a technical position, and I hope that continues. I generally do struggle for challenge so I&amp;rsquo;m open to where my career will take me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>